

KATIF FULLMER designer & developer



ABOUT

With over a decade of experience, I specialize in designing and developing custom websites and applications, utilizing a wide range of technologies while delivering engaging interfaces that focus on user experience, accessibility, performance, and functionality.

I have an insatiable interest in creative problem-solving and love taking on new projects that present complex, measurable data that can be iterated on long after implementation. I work with cross-functional teams to distill complex requirements into thoughtful, thorough, and delightful products.

Over the years, I have come to truly enjoy the process of evaluating the scope of a product providing new business ideas. innovations, and values that meet user needs as well as business objectives. Using an agile workflow, I typically guide clients from research and planning, to conceptualizing with prototypes, and finally to testing and implementation.

I am always eager to learn new skills, and am open to new opportunities and experiences. My days are spent with thoughtful, creative, and honest people and I strive to display all of those qualities as well.



CONTACT

- www.katiefullmer.com



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS IN STUDIO ART / 2008 - 2012

Louisiana State University - Concentration: Graphic Design Baton Rouge, Louisiana

MINOR IN ART HISTORY / 2008 - 2012

Louisiana State University Baton Rouge, Louisiana



EXPERIENCE

HEALTH CONNECTIVE / JUN 2012 - PRESENT Senior UX Designer & Front End Developer in New Orleans, LA

- Provide interactive prototypes, high-fidelity designs, and custom application development for medtech companies and various orthopedic and neuro medical practices.
- Evolve and maintain design system libraries, creating new components and scaling existing assets with the latest features in Figma.
- Ensure projects meet WCAG 2.1 AA standards by advocating for inclusive design best practices.
- Foster professional growth of junior designers, providing feedback and opportunities for collaboration.
- Convey design ideas and solutions to peers, clients, and stakeholders in weekly meetings.

BEACHVIEW ENERGY / JULY 2012 - FEB 2020 Freelance Graphic Designer in Brunswick, GA

Designed various brand and promotional materials including customer newsletters, website graphics, and social media assets.

DIG MAGAZINE / AUG 2011 - JUN 2012

Graphic Designer in Baton Rouge, LA

Created key visual assets on strict deadlines for weekly publication. In addition to providing editorial layouts, I designed visuals for advertisements, posters, media kits, and brand identities.



SKILLS

Creative Direction Branding

UX/UI Design

Prototyping

Front End Development Agile Methodologies

Design Systems

Responsive Web Design WCAG Accessibility Standards Figma